class Data1 {
  List<Map> keralaquizQuestions = [
    {
      'question': '1. What is the capital city of Kerala?',
      'answers': ['Thiruvananthapuram', 'Kochi', 'Kozhikode', 'Thrissur'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Thiruvananthapuram
    },
    {
      'question': '2. Which river is known as thelifeline of Kerala?',
      'answers': ['Periyar', 'Bharathapuzha', 'Pamba', 'Chaliyar'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 2, // Pamba
    },
    {
      'question': '3. Which dance form is native to Kerala?',
      'answers': ['Bharatanatyam', 'Kathakali', 'Odissi', 'Kuchipudi'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 1, // Kathakali
    },
    {
      'question': '4. What is the traditional attire of men in Kerala?',
      'answers': ['Saree', 'Mundu', 'Dhoti', 'Lehenga'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 1, // Mundu
    },
    {
      'question': '5. Which is the highest peak in Kerala?',
      'answers': [
        'Anamudi',
        'Meeshapulimala',
        'Agasthyakoodam',
        'Chembra Peak'
      ],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Anamudi
    },
    {
      'question': '6. What is the famous backwater destination\nin Kerala?',
      'answers': ['Kumarakom', 'Kovalam', 'Varkala', 'Alappuzha'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 3, // Alappuzha
    },
    {
      'question': '7. Which is the state animal of Kerala?',
      'answers': ['Tiger', 'Elephant', 'Lion', 'Leopard'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 1, // Elephant
    },
    {
      'question':
          '8. What is the name of the traditional martial art\nform of Kerala?',
      'answers': ['Silambam', 'Kalaripayattu', 'Gatka', 'Thang-ta'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 1, // Kalaripayattu
    },
    {
      'question': '9. Who is known as the father of the Kerala\nRenaissance?',
      'answers': [
        'Sree Narayana Guru',
        'Chattampi Swamikal',
        'Ayyankali',
        'Vakkom Moulavi'
      ],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Sree Narayana Guru
    },
    {
      'question': '10. Which is the largest district by area in Kerala?',
      'answers': ['Idukki', 'Palakkad', 'Malappuram', 'Wayanad'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Idukki
    },
  ];
}
class Data2 {
  List<Map> indianQuizQuestions = [
    {
      'question': '1. What is the capital city of India?',
      'answers': ['New Delhi', 'Mumbai', 'Kolkata', 'Chennai'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // New Delhi
    },
    {
      'question': '2. Which river is known as the lifeline of India?',
      'answers': ['Ganges', 'Yamuna', 'Brahmaputra', 'Indus'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Ganges
    },
    {
      'question': '3. What is the national animal of India?',
      'answers': ['Tiger', 'Lion', 'Elephant', 'Leopard'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Tiger
    },
    {
      'question': '4. Who wrote the Indian national anthem, "Jana Gana Mana"?',
      'answers': ['Rabindranath Tagore', 'Mahatma Gandhi', 'Jawaharlal Nehru', 'Subhas Chandra Bose'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Rabindranath Tagore
    },
    {
      'question': '5. What is the highest civilian award in India?',
      'answers': ['Bharat Ratna', 'Padma Bhushan', 'Padma Vibhushan', 'Padma Shri'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Bharat Ratna
    },
    {
      'question': '6. Which is the largest state in India by area?',
      'answers': ['Rajasthan', 'Madhya Pradesh', 'Maharashtra', 'Uttar Pradesh'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Rajasthan
    },
    {
      'question': '7. What is the currency of India?',
      'answers': ['Rupee', 'Rupiah', 'Ringgit', 'Dollar'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Rupee
    },
    {
      'question': '8. Who was the first Prime Minister of India?',
      'answers': ['Jawaharlal Nehru', 'Indira Gandhi', 'Lal Bahadur Shastri', 'Morarji Desai'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Jawaharlal Nehru
    },
    {
      'question': '9. Where is the famous monument Taj Mahal located?',
      'answers': ['Agra', 'Jaipur', 'Delhi', 'Mumbai'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Agra
    },
    {
      'question': '10. Which Indian state is known as the "Land of Five Rivers"?',
      'answers': ['Punjab', 'Haryana', 'Uttarakhand', 'Bihar'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Punjab
    },
  ];
}

class Data3 {
  List<Map> sportsQuizQuestions = [
    {
      'question': '1. In which sport does a player try to hit a\nshuttlecock over a net using a racket?',
      'answers': ['Badminton', 'Tennis', 'Table Tennis', 'Squash'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Badminton
    },
    {
      'question': '2. How many players are there in a rugby league\nteam?',
      'answers': ['13', '15', '11', '9'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // 13
    },
    {
      'question': '3. Which country won the FIFA World Cup in\n2018?',
      'answers': ['France', 'Brazil', 'Germany', 'Spain'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // France
    },
    {
      'question': '4. What is the maximum number of clubs a golfer\nis allowed to carry in their bag during a round of golf?',
      'answers': ['14', '10', '12', '16'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // 14
    },
    {
      'question': '5. Who is the all-time leading scorer in NBA\nhistory?',
      'answers': ['Kareem Abdul-Jabbar', 'LeBron James', 'Michael Jordan', 'Kobe Bryant'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Kareem Abdul-Jabbar
    },
    {
      'question': '6. What is the term used in cricket to describe\nthe act of a bowler dismissing a batsman on the first ball of the match?',
      'answers': ['Golden Duck', 'Silver Duck', 'Bronze Duck', 'Platinum Duck'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Golden Duck
    },
    {
      'question': '7. In which Olympic sport would you perform a\n"pommel horse" routine?',
      'answers': ['Gymnastics', 'Swimming', 'Diving', 'Track and Field'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Gymnastics
    },
    {
      'question': '8. Which tennis player has won the most Grand Slam\nsingles titles?',
      'answers': ['Margaret Court', 'Serena Williams', 'Steffi Graf', 'Martina Navratilova'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Margaret Court
    },
    {
      'question': '9. How many points is a touchdown worth in\nAmerican football?',
      'answers': ['6', '3', '2', '1'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // 6
    },
    {
      'question': '10. Which city hosted the 2016 Summer\nOlympics?',
      'answers': ['Rio de Janeiro', 'Tokyo', 'London', 'Beijing'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Rio de Janeiro
    },
  ];
}

class Data4 {
  List<Map> birdQuizQuestions = [
    {
      'question': '1. Which bird is known for its ability to mimic\nhuman speech?',
      'answers': ['Parrot', 'Eagle', 'Owl', 'Penguin'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Parrot
    },
    {
      'question': '2. Which bird is the fastest animal in the\nworld?',
      'answers': ['Peregrine Falcon', 'Emperor Penguin', 'Albatross', 'Hummingbird'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Peregrine Falcon
    },
    {
      'question': '3. Which bird is the national symbol of the\nUnited States?',
      'answers': ['Bald Eagle', 'Turkey', 'Blue Jay', 'Robin'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Bald Eagle
    },
    {
      'question': '4. Which bird is known for its long migration\njourney, often spanning continents?',
      'answers': ['Arctic Tern', 'Flamingo', 'Toucan', 'Kiwi'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Arctic Tern
    },
    {
      'question': '5. Which bird is the largest living bird\nspecies?',
      'answers': ['Ostrich', 'Cassowary', 'Emu', 'Condor'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Ostrich
    },
    {
      'question': '6. Which bird species is known for its\ndistinctive courtship dance?',
      'answers': ['Bird of Paradise', 'Peacock', 'Puffin', 'Crane'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Bird of Paradise
    },
    {
      'question': '7. Which bird is famous for its ability to dive\nunderwater to catch fish?',
      'answers': ['Penguin', 'Seagull', 'Heron', 'Kingfisher'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 3, // Kingfisher
    },
    {
      'question': '8. Which bird is the national bird of India?',
      'answers': ['Peacock', 'Crow', 'Sparrow', 'Kite'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Peacock
    },
    {
      'question': '9. Which bird is known for its ability to build\nintricate nests?',
      'answers': ['Weaverbird', 'Swan', 'Dove', 'Sparrow'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Weaverbird
    },
    {
      'question': '10. Which bird is often associated with wisdom\nin many cultures?',
      'answers': ['Owl', 'Eagle', 'Hawk', 'Vulture'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Owl
    },
  ];
}


class Data5 {
  List<Map> animalQuizQuestions = [
    {
      'question': '1. Which animal is known as the "king of the\njungle"?',
      'answers': ['Lion', 'Tiger', 'Leopard', 'Cheetah'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Lion
    },
    {
      'question': '2. Which animal is the largest land mammal?',
      'answers': ['Elephant', 'Giraffe', 'Hippo', 'Rhino'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Elephant
    },
    {
      'question': '3. Which animal has the longest\nlifespan?',
      'answers': ['Giant Tortoise', 'Bowhead Whale', 'African Elephant', 'Red Sea Urchin'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Giant Tortoise
    },
    {
      'question': '4. Which animal is known for its ability to\nchange color?',
      'answers': ['Chameleon', 'Octopus', 'Cuttlefish', 'Mimic Octopus'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Chameleon
    },
    {
      'question': '5. Which animal is considered the fastest\nland animal?',
      'answers': ['Cheetah', 'Pronghorn Antelope', 'Horse', 'Greyhound'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Cheetah
    },
    {
      'question': '6. Which animal is known for its long neck?',
      'answers': ['Giraffe', 'Kangaroo', 'Ostrich', 'Emu'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Giraffe
    },
    {
      'question': '7. Which animal is capable of regenerating\nlost limbs?',
      'answers': ['Starfish', 'Salamander', 'Axolotl', 'Lizard'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 2, // Axolotl
    },
    {
      'question': '8. Which animal is known for its hibernation\nduring winter?',
      'answers': ['Bear', 'Squirrel', 'Bat', 'Groundhog'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 3, // Groundhog
    },
    {
      'question': '9. Which animal has the largest brain relative\nto its body size?',
      'answers': ['Sperm Whale', 'Elephant', 'Dolphin', 'Human'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 2, // Dolphin
    },
    {
      'question': '10. Which animal is known as the "ship of the\ndesert"?',
      'answers': ['Camel', 'Horse', 'Donkey', 'Llama'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Camel
    },
  ];
}
class Data6 {
  List<Map> carQuizQuestions = [
    {
      'question': '1. Which car manufacturer produces the\nMustang?',
      'answers': ['Ford', 'Chevrolet', 'Toyota', 'Honda'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Ford
    },
    {
      'question': '2. What does SUV stand for?',
      'answers': ['Sports Utility Vehicle', 'Super Utility Vehicle', 'Special Utility Vehicle', 'Standard Utility Vehicle'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Sports Utility Vehicle
    },
    {
      'question': '3. What car is often referred to as the\n"people\'s car"?',
      'answers': ['Volkswagen Beetle', 'Toyota Corolla', 'Honda Civic', 'Ford Focus'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Volkswagen Beetle
    },
    {
      'question': '4. Which car brand has a logo featuring a\nprancing horse?',
      'answers': ['Ferrari', 'Lamborghini', 'Porsche', 'Bugatti'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Ferrari
    },
    {
      'question': '5. Which country is famous for producing the\nMini Cooper?',
      'answers': ['United Kingdom', 'Germany', 'Italy', 'France'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // United Kingdom
    },
    {
      'question': '6. What car model is often associated with the\nterm "muscle car"?',
      'answers': ['Dodge Challenger', 'Toyota Camry', 'Honda Accord', 'Nissan Altima'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Dodge Challenger
    },
    {
      'question': '7. Which car company produces the Prius, known\nfor its hybrid technology?',
      'answers': ['Toyota', 'Honda', 'Ford', 'Chevrolet'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Toyota
    },
    {
      'question': '8. What is the top speed of the Bugatti Veyron\nSuper Sport, the fastest production car in the world?',
      'answers': ['267 mph', '220 mph', '300 mph', '350 mph'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // 267 mph
    },
    {
      'question': '9. Which car brand is known for its iconic 911\nmodel?',
      'answers': ['Porsche', 'Ferrari', 'Lamborghini', 'Maserati'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Porsche
    },
    {
      'question': '10. What is the best-selling electric car model\nof all time?',
      'answers': ['Tesla Model 3', 'Nissan Leaf', 'Chevrolet Bolt', 'BMW i3'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 1, // Nissan Leaf
    },
  ];
}



class Data7 {
  List<Map> historyQuizQuestions = [
    {
      'question': '1. Who was the first president of the \nUnited States?',
      'answers': ['George Washington', 'Thomas Jefferson', 'Abraham Lincoln', 'John Adams'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // George Washington
    },
    {
      'question': '2. In which year did World War II \nend?',
      'answers': ['1945', '1939', '1941', '1950'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // 1945
    },
    {
      'question': '3. Who wrote "The Communist \nManifesto"?',
      'answers': ['Karl Marx and Friedrich Engels', 'Vladimir Lenin', 'Joseph Stalin', 'Leon Trotsky'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Karl Marx and Friedrich Engels
    },
    {
      'question': '4. What event marked the beginning \nof the French Revolution?',
      'answers': ['Storming of the Bastille', 'Execution of Louis XVI', 'Reign of Terror', 'Napoleon Bonaparte seizing power'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Storming of the Bastille
    },
    {
      'question': '5. Who was the first emperor of \nRome?',
      'answers': ['Augustus', 'Julius Caesar', 'Nero', 'Constantine'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Augustus
    },
    {
      'question': '6. What year did Christopher Columbus \ndiscover America?',
      'answers': ['1492', '1520', '1453', '1533'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // 1492
    },
    {
      'question': '7. Who was the first female Prime \nMinister of the United Kingdom?',
      'answers': ['Margaret Thatcher', 'Theresa May', 'Queen Elizabeth II', 'Indira Gandhi'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Margaret Thatcher
    },
    {
      'question': '8. What was the name of the first \nsuccessful manned mission to the moon?',
      'answers': ['Apollo 11', 'Apollo 13', 'Gemini 4', 'Mercury-Redstone 3'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Apollo 11
    },
    {
      'question': '9. Who was the founder of the Mongol \nEmpire?',
      'answers': ['Genghis Khan', 'Kublai Khan', 'Attila the Hun', 'Timur'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Genghis Khan
    },
    {
      'question': '10. What was the name of the treaty \nthat ended World War I?',
      'answers': ['Treaty of Versailles', 'Treaty of Paris', 'Treaty of Trianon', 'Treaty of Brest-Litovsk'],
      'correctAnswerIndex': 0, // Treaty of Versailles
    },
  ];
}
